propertyroom.com 2014-12-14

# Property Room Privacy Policy

## Privacy Policy

Below please find details on the prevailing privacy practices for Property Room, which will get updated from time-to-time. These privacy practices address the following questions:

  1. What personal information is collected?
  2. Who is collecting the information?
  3. How is your personal information used?
  4. With whom may your personal information be shared?
  5. What are cookies and how are they used?
  6. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your personal information?
  7. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under Property Room’s control?
  8. How can you correct any inaccuracies in your personal information?

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Property Room at Customer Support.  

### 1\. What personal information is collected?

Personal information of yours that we may collect and store includes, but is not limited to, first and last name; home, billing or other physical address (including street name, name of a city or town, state, postal code); email address; telephone number; fax number; credit card information; IP address; bidding activity; shipment activity; returns activity; URL referral data; support communications including email and telephone logs; site search activities; wish list; website usage; any other identifier that permits Property Room to make physical or online contact with you; and any information Property Room collects online from you and maintains in association with your account, such as your Property Room username and Property Room password.

Personal information is collected from you when you voluntarily register for membership services with Property Room. These services include receiving electronic newsletters, purchasing items, and entering contests and participating in other opportunities provided by Property Room. We also collect email addresses from anyone who sends us mail or request technical or other help. This information enables Property Room to improve its site to make your online visits more productive and enjoyable.

Information about your activities on our web pages (such as the pages you access most frequently or the search terms you enter) is collected by tracking Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you surf the web. The computers that deliver the Web pages to you automatically identify your computer by its IP address. When you request a page from our site, our server logs your IP address.

Back to Top

### 2\. Who is collecting the information?

Unless specifically stated otherwise, when you share personal information through our website, you are sharing that information only with Property Room, its related service providers, and, if applicable, the third party vendor providing the purchased item.

Our website may include hyperlinks to unaffiliated third parties’ websites. This privacy policy cannot and does not apply to websites not operated by Property Room. You should consult each website’s privacy policy before providing any personal information to anyone else.

Back to Top

### 3\. How is your personal information used?

Property Room uses the personal information we collect to obtain payment for and to ship the products you purchase, to improve the content of our site, to respond to your inquiries and provide user support, to notify you about updates to our site or promotional offers or for marketing opportunities that we believe will be of interest to you and to investigate violations of our terms and conditions of use.

Back to Top

### 4\. With whom may your personal information be shared?

Except as explicitly described in this privacy policy, Property Room will not sell or share your name, address, phone numbers, email address, financial data or any other information that personally identifies you to third parties without your consent.

By placing an order or bidding on an item, you are granting your consent to allow us to share your information with the law enforcement agency or other third party seller or vendor providing the purchased item. To the extent that you make a purchase, you are granting your consent to allow us to share your information with related service providers (such as a credit card processor for processing payment and a shipping company for shipping your purchase to you), in each case to the extent reasonably necessary to fulfill that order.

Property Room may divulge personal information to a third party service provider (such as a credit card processor) to resolve suspected fraud or other inappropriate use (or abuse) issues. In such an instance, Property Room would divulge the information to resolve the issue whether you or Property Room was suspected of the misuse, and such information would be divulged for the sole and exclusive purpose of resolving allegations of misuse or abuse.

Property Room may also divulge personal information if such information is subpoenaed or requested by a law enforcement agency as part of an investigation. In addition, Property Room may divulge personal information if Property Room believes that its site has been used to commit unlawful acts, or acts that might endanger the health or safety of another user or of the general public.

Lastly, in the event that Property Room or substantially all of its assets are acquired, Property Room would transfer all customer data and other personal information of its users to the new owner.

Back to Top

### 5\. What are cookies and how are they used?

Property Room uses “cookies” to record information. A cookie is a small data file that websites store on your hard drive when you visit them. Cookies allow us to measure activity in our site and to improve your user experience by remembering your password and viewing preferences, and allowing you to visit our site without re-registering. Cookies allow us to determine which areas and features of our site are more popular by measuring user activity.

This information allows us to retain the required information for your bidding and browsing to function and make improvements and updates to improve your Property Room.com experience. Property Room does not use cookies to retrieve any information from your computer.

Most browsers are set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you may set your browser to not accept cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. However, some parts of our site such as the member’s only area (i.e., the bidding area) will not function properly if you choose not to accept cookies.

You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers. Property Room does not control these cookies, and they are not subject to Property Room’s privacy policy.

Back to Top

### 6\. What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of your personal information?

If you indicated when registering that you are interested in receiving offers or information from Property Room, we may occasionally send you information regarding our products and services. If you no longer wish to receive such information, you may do so by editing your Property Room account information.

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies, you will be unable to use those Property Room services that require registration.

Back to Top

### 7\. What kind of security procedures are in place to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of personal information under Property Room’s control?

Your Property Room account information is password protected so that only you have access to it. We strongly recommend that you not divulge your password to anyone.

There are several places on the Property Room site where you can transmit credit card information to complete a purchase transaction, or for verification purposes. Any time we ask for a credit card number we transmit that credit card number in an encrypted format. We use industry standard, SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encryption. Property Room.com stores all your personal information on secure servers and in an encrypted format.

No Internet data transmission can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, Property Room cannot assure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best efforts to ensure its security on our systems.

Under no circumstances, including but not limited to negligence, shall Property Room be liable for any special, incidental or consequential damages that result from the use of the information or materials on Property Room, even if Property Room or its authorized representative has been advised of the possibility of such damages. This section should also be read in conjunction with the full User Agreement found on this site.

Property Room reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Any such changes will be posted online. Questions should be directed to [Customer Support](mailto:customersupport@propertyroom.com).

Back to Top

### 8\. How can you correct any inaccuracies in your personal information?

Property Room believes strongly in providing you with the ability to access and edit the personal information that you have provided us. You may edit your password protected account information at any time by entering the site with your Property Room User ID and Password. If you need to communicate directly with Property Room staff personnel in order to resolve a specific issue, please do so by sending an email to [Customer Support](mailto:customersupport@propertyroom.com).

Back to Top
